let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of these is not a characteristic of fitness?",
    answer: "Fitness is environment-specific.",
    options: [
      "Fitness is environment-specific.",
      "Fitness is species-specific.",
      "Higher reproductive rate means higher fitness.",
      "Fitness should be measured across several generations."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Ecology is the scientific study of interactions among organisms and their ___. (Fill in the blanks)",
    answer: "environment",
    options: [
      "habitat",
      "niche",
      "environment",
      "population"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "\"Enquiry into plants\" is a book written by",
    answer: "Theophrastus",
    options: [
      "Theophrastus",
      "Linnaeus",
      "Malthus",
      "Humboldt"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of these is not a kind of selection",
    answer: "stochastic",
    options: [
      "directional",
      "stochastic",
      "disruptive",
      "stabilising"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Ecology is the scientific study of _______ that determine the distribution and abundance of organisms. (Fill in the blanks)",
    answer: "interactions",
    options: [
      "statics",
      "interactions",
      "dynamics",
      "habitat"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of these is not a step in natural selection?",
    answer: "underpopulation",
    options: [
      "variation",
      "underpopulation",
      "struggle for existence",
      "survival of the fittest"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of these is not a characteristic of fitness?",
    answer: "Fitness works on traits such as size and speed.",
    options: [
      "Fitness is environment-specific.",
      "Fitness is species-specific.",
      "Fitness works on traits such as size and speed.",
      "Fitness should be measured across several generations."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In the Greek word root of Ecology, Oikos refers to",
    answer: "household",
    options: [
      "household",
      "preservation",
      "environment",
      "study"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In the Greek word root of Ecology, logos refers to",
    answer: "study",
    options: [
      "household",
      "preservation",
      "environment",
      "study"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who amongst these is considered the father of Biogeography?",
    answer: "Humboldt",
    options: [
      "Theophrastus",
      "Linnaeus",
      "Malthus",
      "Humboldt"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "For more diversity, the level of disturbance should be",
    answer: "intermediate",
    options: [
      "less",
      "intermediate",
      "more",
      "none of these"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 12,
    question: "Hierarchy emerges almost inevitably through a wide variety of evolutionary processes, for the simple reason that hierarchical structures are _____ (fill in the blank)",
    answer: "stable",
    options: [
      "perfect",
      "imperfect",
      "stable",
      "unstable"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 13,
    question: "\"Groups of actually or potentially interbreeding natural populations which are reproductively isolated from other such groups\" is a definition of",
    answer: "species",
    options: [
      "cells",
      "species",
      "ecosystems",
      "biomes"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 14,
    question: "The emergent principle can be stated as",
    answer: "whole > sum of parts",
    options: [
      "whole = sum of parts",
      "whole < sum of parts",
      "whole > sum of parts",
      "none of these"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 15,
    question: "There is more biodiversity in areas with",
    answer: "more competition, more predation",
    options: [
      "less competition, less predation",
      "less competition, more predation",
      "more competition, more predation",
      "more competition, less predation"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 16,
    question: "The mitochondrion is a/an",
    answer: "sub-cellular organelle",
    options: [
      "sub-cellular organelle",
      "cell",
      "tissue",
      "organ"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 17,
    question: "\"The diversity that exists among different geographies\" is",
    answer: "gamma biodiversity",
    options: [
      "alpha biodiversity",
      "beta biodiversity",
      "gamma biodiversity",
      "delta biodiversity"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 18,
    question: "\"The diversity that exists within an ecosystem\" is",
    answer: "alpha biodiversity",
    options: [
      "alpha biodiversity",
      "beta biodiversity",
      "gamma biodiversity",
      "delta biodiversity"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 19,
    question: "The hierarchical system was given by",
    answer: "Simon",
    options: [
      "Simon",
      "Watson",
      "Hutchinson",
      "Humboldt"
    ]
},

{
    numb: 20,
    question: "The laboratory approach to ecology uses",
    answer: "experiments",
    options: [
      "equation",
      "models",
      "observations",
      "experiments"
    ]
}
];
